{
  "topic": "6.3",
  "title": "Логарифмические уравнения",
  "types": [
    {
      "id": "6.3.1",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(8 - x) = \\log_{5} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(14 - x) = \\log_{3} 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{7}(12 - x) = \\log_{7} 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(15 - x) = \\log_{2} 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(20 - x) = \\log_{5} 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(9 - x) = \\log_{3} 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{4}(11 - x) = \\log_{4} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{6}(13 - x) = \\log_{6} 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{8}(18 - x) = \\log_{8} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{9}(10 - x) = \\log_{9} 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(9 - x) = \\log_{5} 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{7}(16 - x) = \\log_{7} 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 12 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(7 - x) = \\log_{3} 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(22 - x) = \\log_{2} 11 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 11 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{4}(25 - x) = \\log_{4} 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 20 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(19 - x) = \\log_{3} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 17 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{6}(17 - x) = \\log_{6} 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(14 - x) = \\log_{5} 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{7}(21 - x) = \\log_{7} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 19 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.1.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(30 - x) = \\log_{2} 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 24 }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6.3.2",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 2) = \\log_{2} 11 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 13 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 5) = \\log_{2} 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 1) = \\log_{2} 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 4) = \\log_{2} 12 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 6) = \\log_{2} 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 11 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 3) = \\log_{2} 9 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 12 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 7) = \\log_{2} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 10) = \\log_{2} 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 8) = \\log_{2} 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 12 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 9) = \\log_{2} 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 11) = \\log_{2} 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 13) = \\log_{2} 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 15) = \\log_{2} 9 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 24 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 20) = \\log_{2} 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 28 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 4) = \\log_{2} 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 2) = \\log_{2} 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 6) = \\log_{2} 13 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 19 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 5) = \\log_{2} 10 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 15 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 12) = \\log_{2} 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 15 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.2.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 14) = \\log_{2} 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6.3.3",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{4}(x - 4) = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 68 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(x - 2) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 11 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(x - 1) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 26 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 6) = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 22 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{7}(x - 3) = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 10 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{8}(x - 4) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 68 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{9}(x - 5) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 86 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(x - 10) = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 37 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 1) = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 33 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{4}(x - 7) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 23 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(x - 6) = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 11 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{6}(x - 5) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 41 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(x - 4) = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 85 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 9) = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 17 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{7}(x - 2) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 51 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{4}(x - 12) = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 16 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{5}(x - 8) = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 133 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{3}(x - 1) = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{2}(x - 15) = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 19 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.3.3.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\log_{4}(x - 20) = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 84 }
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
